I
أنا
I just woke up.
لقد استيقظت للتو
I thought it was some lecher.
ظننت أنه أحد السفهاء
You had me come to your villa.
أمرتني أن آتي إلى هذا القصر الملحق
You don't have another purpose, do you?
أليس لك غرض آخر؟
What do you think?
ما رأيك أنت؟
Follow me.
الحق بي
What exactly are you taking me to see?
ماذا تريد أن تريني بالضبط؟
You had me come to your villa.
جعلتني آتي إلى هذا القصر الملحق
Just to keep being a pig-tending maid?
لأواصل كوني خادمة تربي الخنازير
Where exactly did I offend you?
بماذا أسأت إليك أصلًا؟
Why do you all like raising pigs so much?
لماذا أنتم جميعًا تحبون تربية الخنازير؟
Ru Feng.
رو فنغ
My lord.
سيدي
Take them away.
خذها إلى الخارج
M-My lord...
س... سيدي
Wasn't it you who ordered me to...
ألم تأمرني أن أحضرها
...search everywhere for them?
بعد أن أبحث عنها في كل مكان؟
Why send them away now?
فلماذا نرسلها الآن؟
My lord, there's one more thing.
سيدي، هناك أمر آخر
Speak.
تكلّم
Which guest room should I arrange for the Fifth Princess...
في أي غرفة أُسكن الأميرة الخامسة
...to stay in?
من غرف الضيوف؟
The one closest to your bedroom...
أهي الأقرب إلى مخدعك
...or the one farthest away?
أم الأبعد؟
What do you think?
ما رأيك أنت؟
I say...
أنا أقول
What do you all think?
وأنتم ماذا تقولون؟
Brother.
أخي
Do you think A Lan was kidnapped by the assassin?
أتظن أن آ لان خُطفت على يد قتلة مأجورين؟
The assassin wasn't after her.
لم يكونوا يستهدفونها
Then where could she have gone?
إذًا إلى أين يمكن أن تكون ذهبت؟
To put it bluntly...
بصراحة
...it's all that He scoundrel's fault.
اللوم كله على ذلك اللص المسمّى هِه
If it weren't for chasing him...
لولا مطاردته
...I would never have left the Meng residence.
لما غادرتُ بيت مينغ
How could A Lan have gone missing?
ولما اختفت آ لان
Young Master.
السيد الشاب
Young Lady.
آنسة
Well?
كيف الأمر؟
Any news?
هل من أخبار؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد
Keep sending people to search.
واصلوا إرسال الناس للبحث
Yes.
أمرك
Ru Feng.
رو فنغ
I saw inside the room...
رأيت داخل الغرفة
...there are girl's clothes.
ملابس فتاة
That is...
تلك...
...that is what my lord ordered to be prepared for the princess.
أعدّها سيدي للأميرة
I didn't expect...
لم أتوقع
...your lord to be so considerate.
أن سيدك شديد العناية فعلًا
I was just wondering what to wear...
كنت أفكر حين أبدّل ثيابي بعد قليل
...when I change and bathe later.
ماذا سأرتدي
Princess.
أيتها الأميرة
Do you need anyone to attend to you?
هل تحتاجين من يخدمك؟
Our villa has no maidservants.
لا توجد خادمات في هذا القصر الملحق
No, no need.
لا، لا حاجة
Then this subordinate will take his leave.
إذًا أستأذن بالانصراف
A Lan.
آ لان
What is it?
هل هناك أمر؟
My lord.
سيدي
My lord, what are you...
سيدي، ما هذا...
You just called out 'Fifth Princess'...
لقد ناديتَ قبل قليل: الأميرة الخامسة
What Fifth Princess?
أي أميرة خامسة؟
Didn't you notice anything unusual?
ألم تلاحظ شيئًا غير طبيعي؟
N-No, I didn't.
لا... لا
Assassin!
هناك قتلة مأجورون!
There's an assassin!
قتلة مأجورون!
He's already gone.
لقد رحلوا
In the future...
لاحقًا
...be more alert.
كوني أكثر يقظة
Taking a bath in broad daylight?
لماذا تستحمين في وضح النهار؟
My lord.
سيدي
Young Master Meng has sent people...
السيد الشاب مينغ أرسل رجالًا
...everywhere inquiring about the Fifth Princess's whereabouts.
يسألون في كل مكان عن مكان الأميرة الخامسة
Moreover, this subordinate also heard...
وسمعتُ أيضًا
...that Young Master Meng particularly likes...
أن السيد الشاب مينغ يحب كثيرًا
...the Fifth Princess disguised as a maid.
الأميرة الخامسة المتنكّرة في هيئة خادمة
He often teaches her to read...
ويعلّمها القراءة والكتابة كثيرًا
...paint, swordplay, and such.
والرسم، واستعراض السيف، وما شابه
And the Fifth Princess...
أما الأميرة الخامسة
...in turn warms Young Master Meng's bed, reads to him...
فتدفئ فراش السيد الشاب مينغ وتقرأ له
...and even attends his baths.
وتخدمه عند الاستحمام أيضًا
I told you so.
قلتُ لك
The Fifth Princess infiltrated the Meng residence...
إن تسلل الأميرة الخامسة إلى بيت مينغ
...it must be for Young Master Meng.
لا بد أنه كان لأجل السيد الشاب مينغ
He is, after all, the foremost of the Four Young Masters of Yunmi.
فهو زعيم سادة يونمي الأربعة
So I say the Fifth Princess likes him...
لذا أقول إن الأميرة الخامسة تحبه
...and wants to get close to him.
وتريد الاقتراب منه
That's perfectly normal, isn't it?
وهذا طبيعي جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
Which room did you put the Fifth Princess in?
في أي غرفة أسكنتَ الأميرة الخامسة؟
Don't worry about that, my lord.
اطمئن يا سيدي
I arranged her in...
لقد أسكنتها في...
...I specifically put her in the east wing room.
تعمدتُ أن أسكنها في الغرفة الشرقية
What? My lord...
ماذا يا سيدي؟
...is it still not far enough?
أليست بعيدة بما يكفي؟
I shouldn't have saved you.
لم يكن ينبغي أن أنقذك
He lifted her skull.
لقد شقّ جمجمتها
The storybooks say...
تقول الحكايات
...a maid must warm the young master's bed.
إن الخادمة يجب أن تدفئ فراش السيد الشاب
In a few days it will be my birthday.
بعد أيام قليلة يحلّ عيد ميلادي
A Lan.
آ لان
What are you planning to give me?
ماذا ستُعدين لتقدميه لي؟
Young Master!
السيد الشاب
You're harassing your servant!
أنت تتحرش بجاريتكم
I know where the map is.
أعرف أين الخريطة
Release the young master.
أطلق سراح السيد الشاب
I'll take you to find the map.
وسآخذك لتجد الخريطة
Don't worry, Young Master.
اطمئن يا سيدي الشاب
I'll be fine.
لن يصيبني مكروه
Some things...
بعض الأمور
...I'll explain to you later.
سأشرحها لك لاحقًا
Seventh Cousin.
ابن الخال السابع
How is the wound on your arm?
كيف صارت إصابة ذراعك؟
It's almost healed.
شُفيت تقريبًا
What's wrong? Let me see.
ما الأمر؟ دعني أرى
It's nothing, nothing.
لا شيء، لا شيء
See?
انظري
No need to worry.
لا داعي للقلق
Is Royal Sister almost here?
هل الأخت الملكية ومن معها على وشك الوصول؟
You stayed at the Meng residence for so many days...
مكثتِ في بيت مينغ كل تلك المدة
...yet at my villa...
وفي قصري الملحق هذا
...you can't even stand one day?
ألا تستطيعين البقاء يومًا واحدًا؟
It's not the same.
هذا مختلف
Indeed, it's not the same.
نعم، مختلف
Here, no one has you...
هنا لا أحد يجعلك
...read, warm beds, or attend baths.
تقرئين، وتدفئين الفراش، وتخدمين الاستحمام
A Lan.
آ لان
Royal Sister!
الأخت الملكية
Seventh Cousin!
ابن الخال السابع
Eldest Brother! Princess!
أخي الأكبر، أيتها الأميرة
Your servant missed you so much!
اشتقتُ إليكِ كثيرًا يا سيدتي
Your servant missed you so much...
اشتقتُ إليكِ حتى إنني
...I couldn't eat or drink.
لا أشتهي الشاي ولا الطعام
Really?
أحقًا؟
How come I feel...
لماذا أشعر أنكِ
...you've gained quite a bit of weight?
ازددتِ سمنة كثيرًا؟
I did gain a few pounds.
حقًا زدتُ بضعة أرطال
Royal Sister.
الأخت الملكية
Let me return to the palace with you today.
سأعود اليوم إلى القصر معكِ
When we return, if Father asks, just say...
وإن سأل والدي الإمبراطور فقولي
...last night I suddenly became enlightened...
إنني البارحة فجأة استعدتُ وعيي
...and regained my senses.
وعادت إليّ قواي العقلية
How about it?
كيف ذلك؟
Five hundred taels!
500 ليانغ
Seven hundred taels!
700 ليانغ
Is there anyone higher than seven hundred taels?
هل من عرض أعلى من 700 ليانغ؟
Young Master Meng
السيد الشاب مينغ
Young Master Meng is here.
وصل السيد الشاب مينغ
He's so handsome and dashing.
إنه وسيم وأنيق حقًا
Indeed.
أجل فعلًا
Young Master Meng.
السيد الشاب مينغ
Do you have something to auction?
هل لديك شيء لبيعه في المزاد؟
So much money!
كل هذا المال!
So much, so much gold!
كل هذا... كل هذا الذهب!
So much gold!
كمية كبيرة من الذهب!
Young Master Meng.
السيد الشاب مينغ
What is this...
ما هذا الذي...
It's too much.
إنه كثير جدًا
Look, this painting is of a girl.
انظر، هذه لوحة لفتاة
Everyone.
أيها السادة
Today, with Prosperous Auction House as witness,
اليوم أطلب من دار مزادات الازدهار أن تشهد
anyone
أيّ شخص
who finds the woman on this notice
يعثر على المرأة في الإعلان
will receive all this gold.
هذا الذهب
All of it will be theirs.
سيكون كله من نصيبه
Young Master Meng, who is this woman?
السيد الشاب مينغ، من هذه المرأة؟
Yes, why spend such a fortune to find her?
نعم، لماذا تنفق كل هذا للعثور عليها؟
She is a maid from my Meng household.
إنها خادمة في دار مينغ
A maid?
خادمة؟
A person I would pay any price
شخص سأدفع أي ثمن
to find.
للعثور عليه
Here.
هيا
Give me a few, give me a few.
أعطني بضع نسخ، أعطني بضع نسخ
Get me a few more.
أحضر لي بضعًا أخرى
Give me one more.
وأعطني واحدة أخرى
Give me one, give me one.
أعطني واحدة، أعطني واحدة
There's enough for everyone.
هناك للجميع، هناك للجميع
Have you seen this woman in the painting?
هل رأيتِ هذه المرأة في اللوحة؟
I haven't seen her.
لم أرها
Miss, have you seen her?
يا آنسة، هل رأيتِها؟
No.
لا
Today's grapes are quite fresh.
عنب اليوم طازج جدًا
Here, try one.
هيا، تذوّقي واحدة
Thank you, Princess.
شكرًا لكِ يا أميرة
Royal Sister.
الأخت الملكية
What's wrong?
ما الأمر؟
Do you have something on your mind?
هل لديكِ ما يشغل بالكِ؟
It's nothing.
لا شيء
I just feel that lately,
أشعر أنه في الأيام الأخيرة
Seventh Cousin has been acting strange.
ابن الخال السابع يتصرف بغرابة
Strange?
بغرابة؟
I always feel
أشعر دائمًا
he's intentionally avoiding me.
أنه يتعمد تجنّبي
Fourth Princess,
الأميرة الرابعة
could it be because
أيمكن أن يكون لأن
Young Master Xiu has someone he likes?
السيد الشاب شيو لديه من يحبها
Usually, when a man likes someone,
عادةً إذا أحب الرجل امرأة
he deliberately keeps his distance from other women.
يتعمد الابتعاد عن النساء الأخريات
According to your servant's guess,
بحسب ما أستنتجه، جاريتكم
Young Master Xiu definitely has someone in his heart.
لا بد أن في قلب السيد الشاب شيو شخصًا
Royal Sister,
الأخت الملكية
you generally shouldn't listen to Xixi.
لا تصغي عادةً لكلام شيشي
You're not just any other woman.
أنتِ لستِ كغيرك من النساء
Who Seventh Cousin likes,
من الذي يحبه ابن الخال السابع؟
don't you have any sense of it at all?
ألا تشعرين بشيء إطلاقًا؟
You two are the male and female leads.
أنتما بطلا القصة
Male and female leads?
بطلا القصة؟
What's that?
وما هذا؟
That's not important.
هذا غير مهم
Royal Sister,
الأخت الملكية
you're with Seventh Cousin every day.
أنتِ مع ابن الخال السابع كل يوم
Haven't you noticed who he's fallen for?
ألم تلاحظي من التي أحبها؟
Maybe we should find a way to help the leads along.
لمَ لا تساعدين بطلي القصة قليلًا؟
Alright.
حسنًا
Let's not talk about him.
لا تتحدثي عنه
What about you?
وأنتِ؟
Me?
أنا؟
Yes.
نعم
You still have a marriage contract with Eldest Cousin.
لديكِ خطبة مع ابن الخال الأكبر
The engagement will definitely be canceled.
ولا بد من إلغاء الخطبة
Besides,
وفوق ذلك
Yuwen Rui doesn't want to marry me either.
يوي وين روي لا يريد الزواج مني أيضًا
Come on, come on.
هيا هيا
Here.
هيا
This
هذا
is fine wine I specially brought from
أحضرته خصيصًا من حانة الخالد السكران
the Drunken Immortal Tavern for Eldest Brother.
نبيذًا فاخرًا للأخ الأكبر
Come on.
هيا
Everyone, try some.
لنتذوقه جميعًا
Here's to us.
هيا، نخبكم
Here.
هيا
Good wine.
نبيذ رائع
With this mood and setting,
في هذا الجو
it's a waste not to play a game.
عدم لعب لعبة سيكون إهدارًا
A Lan, what do you want to play?
ماذا تريد آ لان أن تلعب؟
Truth or Dare.
حقيقة أم جرأة
I swear,
أقسم
if I tell even half a lie,
إن قلتُ نصف كلمة كذب
may I be run over by a carriage.
أموت دهسًا بعربة عند خروجي
Swear.
أقسم
Hurry up.
أسرع
This...
هذا...
Seventh Cousin, hurry up.
ابن الخال السابع، أسرع
I swear,
أقسم
if I tell even half a lie,
إن قلتُ نصف كلمة كذب
may A Lan gain twenty jin.
فلتزد آ لان وزنًا 20 رطلًا
Me?!
أنا...
Fine, fine.
حسنًا حسنًا
If I tell even half a lie, then
إن قلتُ نصف كلمة كذب فـ
may I be struck by lightning.
تضربه صاعقة
That's more like it.
هذا أفضل
Let's go.
هيا
Let's try one round first.
لنجرّب مرة أولى
The bamboo tube points at him.
وجّهي الأنبوب الخيزراني نحوه
You can ask him anything.
يمكنكِ سؤاله أي شيء
Like if he has someone he likes,
مثلًا هل لديه من يحبها
what he's afraid of.
وما الذي يخافه
If he doesn't want to answer,
إن لم يرد الإجابة
then he must choose a dare.
فعليه اختيار الجرأة
Eldest Brother.
يا أخي الأكبر
Do you have someone you like?
هل لديك من تحبها؟
Come on, come on.
هيا هيا
That last one doesn't count.
ما قبل لا يُحسب
Let's do it again.
مرة أخرى
Seventh Cousin.
ابن الخال السابع
Is there anything you want to ask?
هل لديك ما تريد سؤاله؟
Then I'll ask.
إذًا سأَسأل أنا
Royal Sister.
الأخت الملكية
What kind of man do you like?
أي نوع من الرجال تحبين؟
An upright and honorable man,
صريح ونزيه
a man I can entrust my life to.
رجل يمكن الاعتماد عليه مدى الحياة
So that's the type Royal Sister likes.
إذًا الأخت الملكية تحب هذا النوع
Come on.
هيا
Let's continue.
تابعوا
Seventh Cousin.
ابن الخال السابع
It's your turn.
حان دورك
Then I'll ask.
إذًا سأسأل
Do you have a woman you like?
هل أحببتَ فتاة؟
I choose dare.
أختار الجرأة
A dare, huh?
الجرأة إذًا؟
Then the dare is
إذًا الجرأة هي
to kiss the person next to you.
قبّل الشخص بجانبك مرة
Seventh Cousin,
ابن الخال السابع
you should choose truth instead.
اختر الحقيقة أفضل
Do you have someone you like?
هل لديك من تحبها؟
I never expected it, Seventh Cousin.
لم أتوقع ذلك، ابن الخال السابع
You've hidden it quite well.
لقد أخفيت الأمر جيدًا
Come on, come on.
هيا هيا
Continue, continue. This time, it's my turn.
تابعوا تابعوا، هذه المرة أنا
Not me, not me.
ليس أنا، ليس أنا
The dare is to kiss the person next to you.
أما الجرأة فهي أن تقبّل من بجانبك مرة
Me?
أنا...
Let me see.
دعيني أرى...
Seventh Cousin.
ابن الخال السابع
Look at where the bamboo tube is pointing.
انظر إلى موضع هذا الأنبوب الخيزراني
It's still you.
إذًا أنتِ مجددًا
Then I'll ask another one.
حسنًا، سأطرح سؤالًا آخر
Is the person you like here?
هل الشخص الذي تحبه موجود هنا؟
A Lan, I think you're doing this on purpose.
آ لان، أراك تفعلين ذلك عمدًا
I'm not telling you.
لن أخبرك أبدًا
I've noticed you've been getting mischievous lately, you little fool.
اكتشفتُ يا حمقاء أنكِ صرتِ تتعلمين السوء مؤخرًا
Isn't that right? Let me tell you.
أليس كذلك؟ اسمعي، سأقول لك
This is a gentleman's game.
هذه لعبة شريفة
You, come here.
تعالي إليّ
Come here.
تعالي
Have you been learning bad things?
هل تعلمتِ السوء؟
Seventh Cousin!
ابن الخال السابع
You're still running? Let me hit you once.
وما زلتِ تهربين! دعيني أضربك مرة
Royal Sister, look at him!
الأخت الملكية، انظري إليه
Alright.
حسنًا
Just once, just once.
مرة واحدة فقط، مرة واحدة
Come here. Be careful.
تعالي، انتبهي
Slow down, slow down.
تمهّلي، تمهّلي
So many?
كل هذا؟
Let me see.
دعيني أرى
Why are there so many 'return safely' wishes?
لماذا هناك الكثير من “عودة سالمة”؟
What did you wish for?
ما الأمنية التي تمنّيتها؟
That's my only wish right now.
ليس لدي الآن سوى أمنية واحدة
I can't tell you.
لا أستطيع إخبارك
You can't help me make it come true anyway.
وأنت لا تستطيع تحقيقها لي
Any wish you want to come true,
أي أمنية تريدين تحقيقها
I will help you achieve it.
سأساعدك على تحقيقها كلها
Really?
حقًا؟
Then I'll only let you take a peek.
إذًا لن أريك إلا لمحة واحدة
Alright, alright.
حسنًا، حسنًا
Are you two done yet?
هل انتهيتما أنتما الاثنان؟
Let's go, let's go.
هيا هيا هيا
Let's keep drinking.
تابعوا الشرب
Let's go back and keep drinking.
نعود ونكمل الشرب
Let's go, let's go.
هيا هيا هيا
Let me tell you.
أقول لك
We won't go home until we're drunk.
لن نعود حتى نسكر
Let's go.
هيا
Eldest Cousin.
ابن الخال الأكبر
Both you and A Lan want to cancel the engagement.
أنت وآ لان تريدان فسخ الخطبة
After returning to the palace,
بعد العودة إلى القصر
I will also advise Father Emperor.
سأقنع والدي الإمبراطور أيضًا
Once we find the person who stole the map,
حالما نعثر على سارق الخريطة
My engagement with her will be decided accordingly.
ستُحسم خطبتي منها عندئذ
Are you sure that with that poisoned fake map,
أمتأكد أن بتلك الخريطة المزيفة المسمومة
we can find the assassin?
يمكننا العثور على القاتل؟
We'll see in two days.
سنعرف بعد يومين
You all should stay at the villa tonight.
ستبيتون الليلة في هذا القصر الجانبي
Leave tomorrow.
وترحلون غدًا
Keep drinking.
تابعوا الشرب
Go home.
إلى البيت
Careful, careful, careful.
انتبه، انتبه، انتبه
When you wake up, you can go home.
حين تستيقظ ستعود إلى البيت
Do you want to go home that badly?
أتشتاق إلى البيت إلى هذا الحد؟
Want to go home.
أريد العودة إلى البيت
This little thing is quite a looker, huh?
يا لك من لطيف، مظهرك ليس سيئًا
Get dressed and get up.
ارتدِ ثيابك وانهض
A Zi.
آ زي
Last night, we...
الليلة الماضية نحن...
Last night you drank too much.
الليلة الماضية شربتَ كثيرًا
I was afraid you'd feel unwell if you woke up in the night,
خشيت أن تستيقظ منتصف الليل وتشعر بتوعك
so I slept nearby.
فنمتُ إلى جانبك
Unexpectedly, I fell asleep.
ولم أشعر حتى غلبني النوم
A Zi.
آ زي
Men and women should maintain propriety.
هناك حدود بين الرجال والنساء
You're right.
أنتِ على حق
Now that you have a woman you like,
والآن لديكِ فتاة تحبها
in the future,
لاحقًا
I will be more careful.
سأنتبه لذلك
Who is the woman Seventh Cousin likes?
من الفتاة التي يحبها ابن الخال السابع؟
Have I met her?
هل رأيتها من قبل؟
No.
لا
How did Yuwen Rui get into my bed?
كيف جاء يوي وين روي إلى سريري؟
He really is quite handsome.
إنه وسيم فعلًا
Fifth Princess.
الأميرة الخامسة
Doesn't this count as taking advantage of someone?
أهذا استغلال لضعف شخص؟
I wiped it for you.
مسحتُه لك
Don't mind it.
لا تأخذي الأمر بحساسية
What were you trying to do while I was asleep?
ماذا كنت تنوي أن تفعل وأنا نائمة؟
You moved, that's why I fell.
أنتِ من تحركتِ بعشوائية فسقطتُ
You weren't doing it on purpose, were you?
لا تقل إنكِ فعلتِ ذلك عمدًا؟
On purpose?
عمدًا؟
I deliberately let you fall on me to attack me?
تعمدتُ أن أجعلك تسقط عليّ لتهاجمني؟
For what purpose?
ولماذا أفعل ذلك؟
That's true.
صحيح
Since the Fifth Princess has been so forward with me,
الأميرة الخامسة تتجرأ عليّ هكذا
I can only respond in kind.
فلا يسعني إلا أن أرد بالطريقة نفسها
Return the favor.
وأعيدها عليكِ
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm not like you.
لن أكون مثلك
I don't enjoy taking liberties with others.
تستمتع بمضايقة الآخرين
Consider yourself lucky this time.
هذه المرة سأعتبرها لصالحك
Eldest Brother.
أخي الأكبر
Then I'll escort them back first.
إذًا سأعيدهن أولًا
I'll come find you again in a few days.
سآتي لأراك بعد بضعة أيام
Seventh Cousin!
ابن الخال السابع
Hurry up!
أسرع
Everyone's waiting for you.
الجميع ينتظرك
Coming, coming!
أتيت، أتيت
We're leaving.
سننطلق
Royal Sister.
الأخت الملكية
What's wrong?
ما بكِ؟
Seventh Cousin really does have someone he likes.
ابن الخال السابع لديه من يحب فعلًا
It's probably someone none of us know.
ويبدو أننا لا نعرف تلك الفتاة
Impossible.
مستحيل
He said it himself.
قالها بنفسه
He must be lying.
لا بد أنه كذب
I didn't expect...
لم أتوقع أيضًا
that I would care about this so much.
أنني سأهتم بهذا الأمر إلى هذا الحد
My lord.
سيدي
The Fifth Princess didn't even have breakfast.
الأميرة الخامسة لم تتناول حتى الفطور
She was in such a hurry to leave.
وتريد الرحيل على عجل
It seems...
يبدو
she's unwilling to stay at this villa a moment longer.
أنها لا تريد البقاء في هذا القصر الجانبي لحظة
I can see it now.
لقد اتضح لي الأمر
The Fifth Princess truly does not like you.
الأميرة الخامسة لا تحبك حقًا
This villa...
وهذا القصر الجانبي
she probably won't come back to again.
أخشى أنها لن تعود إليه أيضًا
If she ever willingly returns in the future,
وإن عادت يومًا طوعًا
what will you do?
فماذا ستفعل؟
That's absolutely impossible.
هذا مستحيل قطعًا
If the Fifth Princess does come back,
إن عادت الأميرة الخامسة
according to Shadow Guard rules,
فبحسب قواعد الحرس السري
if I lose the bet,
إن خسرتُ الرهان
I'll wear women's clothing.
فسأرتدي ثياب النساء
Fi...
الأميرة...
Fifth Princess!
الأميرة الخامسة
What are you...?
ما هذا الذي تفعلينه؟
Please sit tight and hold on.
اجلسي بثبات وتمسكي جيدًا
This Plot Spirit is about to issue a new mission.
روح الحبكة ستمنحك مهمة جديدة
The... the mountain road is rough.
الطريق الجبلي... ليس سهلًا
Royal Sister, sit more securely.
الأخت الملكية، اجلسي بثبات
Listen carefully.
أصغي جيدًا
The next cannon fodder you need to save
وقود المدافع التالي الذي عليك إنقاذه
is...
هو
Ru Feng.
رو فنغ
Stop the carriage!
توقف
I've thought it over carefully.
فكرتُ في الأمر جيدًا
Staying at this villa
البقاء في هذا القصر الجانبي
is much more interesting than being in the palace.
أمتع بكثير من القصر الإمبراطوري
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
Remember what you said.
تذكّري ما قلتهِ.
My lord.
سيدي.
Princess.
أميرة.
Princess, you are so beautiful.
أميرة، أنتِ جميلة جدًا.
Xixi.
شيشي.
You... don't misunderstand.
أنتِ... لا تسيئي الفهم.
I lost a bet with my lord.
راهنتُ سيدي وخسرتُ الرهان.
No need to say more.
لا داعي للكلام.
I understand everything.
أنا أفهم كل شيء.
What do you understand?
ماذا فهمتِ؟
Some things don't need to be spelled out.
بعض الأمور لا يلزم توضيحها.
Yes.
نعم.
This dress is new.
هذا الثوب جديد.
This is life's trial for us.
هذا ابتلاء الحياة لنا.
It will pass eventually.
وسيمضي في النهاية.
Don't be sad.
لا تحزني.
You wearing this...
وأنتِ بهذا اللباس،
actually looks quite good.
تبدين جميلة في الحقيقة.
I'm saying, next time...
أقول لكِ، في المرة القادمة
when you give me a new mission...
حين تسندين إليّ مهمة جديدة،
can you pick the right moment?
هلّا اخترتِ الوقت المناسب؟
I just got on the carriage away from Yuwen Rui.
ما إن ركبتُ عربة تبتعد عن يوي وين روي،
Then you tell me the next...
حتى أخبرتِني أن التالي
person to save is Ru Feng.
الذي يجب إنقاذه هو رو فنغ.
Are you teaching me how to do my job?
أتعلّمينني كيف أعمل؟
Fine.
حسنًا.
Tell me.
تكلّمي.
In the original plot...
في الحبكة الأصلية،
where does Ru Feng die?
أين يموت رو فنغ؟
How does he die?
وكيف يموت؟
Right in the woods at the foot of this mountain.
في الغابة أسفل هذا الجبل.
As for when he dies...
أما متى يموت،
due to the increased mission difficulty...
فبسبب ترقية صعوبة المهمة،
you will not know.
لن تعرفي
when the cannon fodder meets his end.
متى يهلك وقود للمدافع.
Mission difficulty increased.
ترقية صعوبة المهمة؟
You don't even discuss it with me?
ولا تحتاجين لمشاورتي؟
What do you think?
ما رأيكِ؟
What about Yuwen Rui?
وماذا عن يوي وين روي؟
What?
ماذا؟
Are you worried about him?
أأنتِ قلقة عليه؟
Why would I worry about him?
ولماذا أقلق عليه؟
I'm just thinking...
كنتُ أفكّر فقط
Ru Feng's death...
هل موت رو فنغ
might be related to Yuwen Rui.
قد يكون له علاقة بيوي وين روي.
If Yuwen Rui gave Ru Feng...
إن كان يوي وين روي قد كلّف رو فنغ
some mission...
بمهمة ما،
and sent Ru Feng to carry it out...
وأمره بتنفيذها،
And then...
ثم...
Don't try to trick me into talking again.
لا تحاولي استدراجي للكلام مجددًا.
This Plot Spirit won't fall for your trap again.
روح الحبكة لن تقع في فخك مرة أخرى.
This attitude of yours won't do.
هكذا لا يصح.
Between a human and a Plot Spirit...
بين الإنسان وروح الحبكة،
wouldn't a little more trust be good?
ألا يكون المزيد من الثقة أفضل؟
Cross-dimensional trust is fragile.
الثقة العابرة للأبعاد هشّة.
Goodbye.
وداعًا.
Good luck.
أتمنى لكِ حظًا طيبًا.
I say...
أقول...
Again with this.
دائمًا هكذا.
Princess.
أميرة.
How much longer must we stay...
كم سنبقى في ضيعة السيد يووين
at Lord Yuwen's villa?
الخاصة؟
What's wrong?
ما الأمر؟
You want to leave as soon as we arrive?
ما إن وصلنا حتى تريدين الرحيل؟
Your servant is worried about you.
جاريتكم قلقة عليكِ.
I think Lord Yuwen is very strange.
أرى أن السيد يووين غريب جدًا.
Strange?
غريب؟
Guess what I just saw.
تخمين ماذا رأيتُ للتو؟
What did you see?
ماذا رأيتِ؟
I saw Ru Feng...
رأيتُ رو فنغ
actually practicing swordplay in women's clothing.
يرقص بالسيف وهو يرتدي ثياب النساء!
The skirt was even pink.
وكانت التنورة وردية أيضًا.
Why... why would he?
هو... لماذا يفعل ذلك؟
Ru Feng was evasive...
كان رو فنغ يتلعثم
and unwilling to say more.
ولا يريد أن يقول الكثير.
But your servant understood everything at a glance.
لكنني من نظرة واحدة فهمتُ كل شيء.
Many young masters from noble families...
كثير من أبناء الأسر الرفيعة
have some strange quirks.
لديهم بعض العادات الغريبة.
Like forbidding maids to laugh.
مثلًا يمنعون الخادمات من الضحك،
Not letting their wives appear in public.
ولا يسمحون لنساء البيت بالظهور للناس.
Or, for example...
ومثلًا أيضًا،
forcing their subordinates to dress as women.
يجبرون أتباعهم على التنكّر بزيّ النساء.
So you mean Yuwen Rui is...
إذًا تقصدين أن يوي وين روي...
Lord Yuwen is the last kind.
السيد يووين من النوع الأخير.
After all this time apart...
بعد كل هذا الغياب،
you still have that familiar train of thought.
ما زال تفكيركِ كما هو.
Princess.
أميرة.
Your servant notices Lord Yuwen these past few days...
أرى أن السيد يووين في هذه الأيام
seems quite eager for you to stay at the villa.
يريدكِ أن تبقي في الضيعة.
Could it be he regrets it...
ألا يكون قد ندم
and wants to marry you again?
ويريد الزواج منكِ مجددًا؟
No.
لا.
That's good then.
هذا جيد.
He made you so sad before.
لقد أحزنكِ كثيرًا من قبل،
Now that you've finally come to your senses...
والأميرة بالكاد تجاوزت الأمر الآن.
your servant doesn't want to see...
لا أريد أن أرى
him make you sad again.
أنه يحزنكِ مرة أخرى.
Princess.
أميرة.
Now that everyone knows your mind has recovered...
الآن الجميع يعلم أنكِ استعدتِ رشدكِ.
your marriage arrangement with Lord Yuwen...
زواجكِ من السيد يووين
won't it be difficult to cancel?
ألن يصعب إلغاؤه؟
Don't worry.
اطمئني.
I will not marry him.
لن أتزوجه أبدًا.
Princess.
أميرة.
Didn't you say...
ألم تقولي
these past days...
إنكِ في هذه الأيام
you've been staying at the Meng residence?
كنتِ تقيمين في بيت مينغ؟
So, what is Young Master Meng like?
كيف هو السيد الشاب مينغ؟
He's talented in both arts and war, and fiercely protective of his own.
هو بارع أدبًا وقتالًا ويحمي خاصته بشدة.
Why?
ما الأمر؟
It's nothing.
لا شيء.
Young Master Meng...
السيد الشاب مينغ
and the Fifth Princess...
الأميرة الخامسة
are a perfect match.
ثنائي مثالي حقًا.
I wonder if that heartless little black one...
لا أدري إن كان شياو هيي عديم الإحساس
misses me or not.
قد اشتاق إليّ أم لا.
Let's take A Lan's portrait and ask around.
لنأخذ صورة آ لان ونسأل في كل مكان.
Maybe someone has seen her.
لعلّ أحدًا رآها.
Lord He.
السيد هِه.
Miss Meng.
الآنسة مينغ.
Lord He, your visit to the Meng residence...
قدوم السيد هِه إلى بيت مينغ...
His Majesty ordered me to investigate the matter of the assassin.
جلالته أمرني بالتحقيق في أمر القتلة.
Lord He.
السيد هِه.
A maid from my residence is missing.
إحدى خادماتي اختفت من بيتي.
She may have been abducted by the assassin.
قد يكون القتلة قد خطفوها.
Could you investigate this for me, my lord?
هل يمكنك أن تتحقق من الأمر لأجلي؟
This is her.
هي هذه.
Her name is A Lan.
اسمها آ لان.
I will inform you as soon as I have any news.
حالما تصلني أخبار سأخبركِ فورًا.
Miss Meng.
الآنسة مينغ.
There is something I would like...
هناك شيء أريده.
On my brother's birthday...
في يوم عيد ميلاد أخي،
It's all because of that petty thief I left the Meng residence.
بسبب هذا اللص اضطررتُ لمغادرة بيت مينغ.
Otherwise, how could A Lan have gone missing?
وإلا فكيف يمكن أن تختفي آ لان؟
My lord.
سيدي.
He is likely part of the same group as the assassin.
من المحتمل أنه من جماعة القتلة نفسها.
Once I catch that petty thief named He...
حين أمسك هذا اللص المسمّى هِه،
this young lady will definitely tear him to pieces!
سأمزّقه إربًا إربًا!
My lord, you just said you had something for me?
سيدي، قلتَ للتو إن لديك شيئًا لتعطيني إياه؟
Lord He
السيد هِه
Do you think this petty thief looks like you?
أتقول إن هذا اللص يشبهك؟
They do seem somewhat similar.
يبدو أنه يشبهني قليلًا فعلًا.
Look more carefully.
انظر جيدًا.
How could they be alike?
كيف يمكن أن يشبهه؟
Lord He has distinct brows and eyes.
السيد هِه حاجباه حاجبان، وعيناه عينان.
This thief has a pointy face and beady eyes.
هذا اللص فمه حاد ووجهه كوجه قرد.
He looks dishonest at first glance.
من النظرة الأولى يتضح أن نيته فاسدة.
How can he compare to you?
كيف له أن يُقارن بك؟
Don't you agree?
أليس كذلك؟
Miss Meng.
الآنسة مينغ
I have urgent business to attend to.
لديّ أمر مهم عليّ إنجازه.
I must take my leave now.
سأذهب لأتولى عملي أولًا.
Let's go.
هيا.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب
I ordered an investigation into A Lan's whereabouts.
أمرتُ رجالي بالتحري عن مكان آ لان.
We discovered something strange.
فاكتشفنا أمرًا غريبًا.
Speak.
تكلّم.
A clerk from the tailor shop in the next alley
عامل متجر الملابس الجاهزة في الزقاق المجاور
said that two days before your birthday,
قال إنه قبل يومين من عيد ميلادك،
he accidentally saw the Grand Chancellor and A Lan
رأى الصدر الأعظم وآ لان مصادفةً
talking by the back door.
يتحدثان عند الباب الخلفي.
But he was too far away
لكن كان بعيدًا،
to hear what they said.
فلم يستطع أن يسمع بوضوح.
Investigate the relationship between A Lan and Yuwen Rui.
اذهب وتحقق من علاقة آ لان بيوي وين روي.
Yes.
نعم.